Being a cop is tough. But in Saigon, 1968, being a cop is crazy.
Off Limits is a action, crime, drama film directed by Christopher Crowe.
McGriff and Albaby are probably doing the worst law enforcement
job in the world - they are plain clothes U.S.
military policemen on duty in war-time Saigon.
However, their job becomes even harder when they start
investigating the serial killings of local prostitutes.
Their prime suspect is high ranking U.S.
Army officer which brings their lives in danger.
Buck McGriff, played by Willem Dafoe.
Albaby Perkins, played by Gregory Hines.
Dix, played by Fred Ward.
Nicole, played by Amanda Pays.
Colonel Dexter Armstrong, played by Scott Glenn.
Maurice, played by Keith David.
Off Limits is a 1988 action-thriller film set during the Vietnam War starring
Willem Dafoe and Gregory Hines and directed by Christopher Crowe.
The term "off limits" referred to the area where the original crime took
place, an area of Saigon off limits to military personnel.
The name of the film was changed to Saigon or Saigon: Off Limits
when it was released throughout the rest of the world.
The film marks Willem Dafoe's second Vietnam War film.
He was assisted in preparing for this role by Vietnam Veteran and
former Counterintelligence Special Agent Ed Murphy.
Dafoe had previously starred in Platoon and would go on to play roles in
Born on the Fourth of July and Flight of the Intruder.
Although set during the war, the tale is more of a
mystery than a story about the war.
The film explores themes of helicopter, undercover, racism, prostitution.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.